Shot everywhere o shot here shot shot shot here it's dangerous
here bro before 1 Sunday worked than 1/2 fair looking for job.
Came to make a Dog Walker here now,
man.
He said he needs to teach me some training techniques.
Because his dog requires some commands.
I'm lucky,
man.
Let's go,
got old.
She's so fucking beautiful.
This one is working.
I go 1 round with it 1 little longer,
but 2 3 I can't,
you know,
it's just my vision 1 day before.
That way it's also better for me with pleasure.
Bro, come on,
beauty,
but I've already left everything a little apart.
You take it,
I'm going to give 1 attack on a few little things also worth Cara,
worth brother brigadão mano until the next one there I wait for you,
closed brother valeu I send you in the zap
crazy.
I'm closing a stop for the week,
man,
so let's take it there
That.
Here everything is within the darkness.
Hand,
O Juninho here bro a deal at the cheva,
I arrived bro I went to borrow a stop,
he said, O bro,
I'll give you a deal there.
But how much is it when it touches your heart?
Then it broke,
man.
It has value,
it has no price.
Bro,
that's the difference.
You know,
relating to people won't.
The customer is on.
I just went for a dog walk.
I feel like I'm taking advantage of opportunities when they're coming along,
but I don't have a plan.
What is the planning?
What I want with money is really being a big challenge for me.
Now heaven is our lady.
Bro even tastes it,
it's in the smell now,
bro.
The guy said he unwinds for me in the bathroom and
will see if I can sleep here and also leave the car here.
See that everyone else is complaining,
I'm happy uncle car here,
oh clean.
And it's us with a lot of ideas for the week with this positivity,
the week starts this way,
so I'm sure you'll plant better things there in your life.
It took a while,
okay.
Follow there until tomorrow,
we're together haha.